(Sheldon:)My quantum gravity's
positively Ioopy!
(Penny:)Who's the duchess?
(Leonard:)One of the people
that lives in his head.
(Amy:)I hope he's this distraught
if he ever breaks up with me.
(Leonard:)Well, if he does, I'll see
if my bear has a friend.
(Penny:)Sheldon, have you ever considered
not rushing into something new?
(Penny:)I mean, why don't you
take your time, enjoy your freedom?
(Penny:)Maybe something new
to study will find you.
(Sheldon:)That's actually not bad advice.
(Sheldon:)You know, I didn't seek out
string theory.
(Sheldon:)It just hit me
over the head one day.
(Amy:)How does that happen?
(Sheldon:)A bully chased me through
the school library
(Sheldon:)and hit me over the head with
the biggest book he could find.
OK, how about we toast
your new-found freedom?
(Sheldon:)Normally I refrain from alcohol,
(Sheldon:)but since my cerebral cortex is
twiddling its proverbial thumbs,
(Sheldon:)why not soak it in grape juice
(Sheldon:)that's been predigested
by a fungus?
(Penny:)And you wonder why other
children beat you with books.